A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, Officers' Actions, SG 16.3 FA474
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Foundation records, Officers' Actions, SG 16.3
1927-2017
1960-2000
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Foundation
FA474
43.66 Cubic Feet 111 letter document boxes, 1 record storage box, and 1 half-letter document box
Conditions Governing Access note
Records more than 10 years old are open for research, with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) or audiovisual material (audio cassettes, VHS, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact a RAC archivist for further instruction.
Scope and Contents
Types of records include: officers actions, grant and fellowship material.
Arrangement
As received
- Accession 1, 1927-1985; 1; 24.88 Cubic Feet 65 letter document boxes and 1 half-letter document box
  - Agriculture, Fellowships, 1955-1959 (Box 1, Folder 1-5)
  - Agriculture, Fellowships and Scholarships, 1960-1963 (Box 2, Folder 6-12)
  - Agriculture, Fellowships and Scholarships, 1963-1965 (Box 3, Folder 13-18)
  - Agriculture, Fellowships and Scholarships, 1966-1968 (Box 4, Folder 19-24)
  - Agriculture, Fellowships and Scholarships, 1968-1969 (Box 5, Folder 25-27)
  - Agricultural Sciences, Fellowships and Scholarships, 1970-1972 (Box 5, Folder 28-30)
  - Agricultural Sciences, Fellowships, Scholarships, and Traineeship, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Agricultural Sciences, Fellowships and Scholarships, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Agricultural Sciences, Fellowships, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Agricultural Sciences, Fellowships and Traineeships, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Agricultural Sciences, Fellowships, 1977-1978, 1983-1985 (Box 6, Folder 35-39)
  - Agriculture, Grants-in-Aid, New York, 1955-1962 (Box 7, Folder 40-45)
  - Agriculture, Grants-in-Aid, 1963-1967 (Box 8, Folder 46-50)
  - Agriculture, Grants-in-Aid, 1968-1969 (Box 9, Folder 51-52)
  - Agricultural Sciences, Grants-in-Aid, 1970-1978, 1983-1985 (Box 9, Folder 53-64)
  - Arts and Humanities, Fellowships & Scholarships, 1971-1973 (Box 10, Folder 65-67)
  - Arts, Grants-in-Aid, 1965-1969 (Box 10, Folder 68-69)
  - Arts and Humanities, Grants-in-Aid, 1970-1973 (Box 10, Folder 70-73)
  - Arts, Grants-in-Aid, 1974-1977 (Box 10, Folder 74-77)
  - Arts, Grants-in-Aid, 1978-1983 (Box 11, Folder 78-83)
  - Arts and Humanities, Grants-in-Aid, 1984-1985 (Box 11, Folder 84-85)
  - Biomedical Research, Fellowships, New York, 1955-1959 (Box 11, Folder 86)
  - Biomedical Sciences, Fellowships and Scholarships, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 87)
  - Biomedical Sciences, Fellowships and Scholarships, 1972-1973 (Box 12, Folder 88-89)
  - Biomedical Research, Grants-in-Aid, 1955-1959 (Box 12, Folder 90-93)
  - Biomedical Sciences, Grants-in-Aid, 1971-1973 (Box 12, Folder 94-96)
  - China, 1933-1941 (Box 12, Folder 97)
  - China, 1933-1942 (Box 13, Folder 98-99)
  - Conquest of Hunger, Fellowships, 1979-1982 (Box 13, Folder 100-104)
  - Conquest of Hunger, Grants-in-Aid, 1979-1982 (Box 13, Folder 105-108)
  - Division of Medical and Public Health, New York, Grants-in-Aid, 1951-1952 (Box 13, Folder 109)
  - Division of Medical and Public Health, New York, Grants-in-Aid, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 110)
  - Division of Medical and Public Health, New York, Allocations and Miscellaneous, 1951-1955 (Box 14, Folder 111)
  - Education for Development, Fellowships, 1979-1985 (Box 14, Folder 112-118)
  - Education for Development, Grants-in-Aid, 1979-1985 (Box 15, Folder 119-124)
  - Equal Opportunity, Grants-in-Aid, 1979-1985 (Box 15, Folder 125-131)
  - European Rehabilitation, Allocations, 1948-1952 (Box 15, Folder 132)
  - General, Grants-in-Aid, 1950-1969 (Box 15, Folder 133-135)
  - Health Sciences, Fellowships & Scholarships, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 136)
  - Health Sciences and Health Sciences/Reproductive Biology, Fellowships, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 137)
  - Health Sciences, Fellowships and Reproductive Biology Fellowships, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 138)
  - Health Sciences, Fellowships, 1977-1985 (Box 16, Folder 139-147)
  - Health Sciences, Grants-in-Aid, 1974-1981 (Box 16, Folder 148-155)
  - Health Sciences, Grants-in-Aid, 1982-1985 (Box 17, Folder 156-159)
  - Humanities, New York, Fellowships, 1929-1946 (Box 17, Folder 160-163)
  - Humanities, New York, Fellowships, 1947-1959 (Box 18, Folder 164-167)
  - Humanities, Paris, Fellowships, 1939 (Box 18, Folder 168)
  - Humanities, Fellowships and Scholarships, 1960-1962 (Box 18, Folder 169-171)
  - Humanities and Social Sciences, Fellowships and Scholarships, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 172)
  - Humanities and Social Sciences, Fellowships and Scholarships, 1964-1967 (Box 19, Folder 173-177)
  - Humanities and Social Sciences, Fellowships and Scholarships, 1968-1970 (Box 20, Folder 178-180)
  - Humanities, Fellowships and Scholarships, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 181)
  - Humanities, Fellowships, 1975-1983 (Box 20, Folder 182-190)
  - Humanities, New York, Grants-in-Aid, 1932-1936 (Box 20, Folder 191)
  - Humanities, New York, Grants-in-Aid, 1937-1949 (Box 21, Folder 192-197)
  - Humanities, New York, Grants-in-Aid and Allocations, 1950-1956 (Box 22, Folder 198)
  - Humanities, New York, Grants-in-Aid, 1951-1958 (Box 22, Folder 199-203)
  - Humanities, New York, Grants-in-Aid, 1959 (Box 23, Folder 204)
  - Humanities, Paris, Grants-in-Aid, 1930-1931, 1939-1940 (Box 23, Folder 205)
  - Humanities, Grants-in-Aid, 1960-1962 (Box 23, Folder 206-208)
  - Humanities and Social Sciences, Grants-in-Aid, 1963-1964 (Box 23, Folder 209-210)
  - Humanities and Social Sciences, Grants-in-Aid, 1965-1970 (Box 24, Folder 211-216)
  - Humanities, Grants-in-Aid, 1973-1983 (Box 25, Folder 217-227)
  - Hungarian Refugee Program, 1956-1959 (Box 25, Folder 228)
  - Inter-Program, Grants-in-Aid, 1970 (Box 26, Folder 229)
  - Inter-Departmental, Grants-in-Aid, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 230)
  - Interdisciplinary, Grants-in-Aid, 1972-1978 (Box 26, Folder 231-237)
  - Interprogram, Grants-in-Aid, 1983-1985 (Box 26, Folder 238-240)
  - International Health Division, 1932-1950 (Box 26, Folder 241-243)
  - International Health Division, Miscellaneous, 1933-1935, 1941-1945, 1949-1951 (Box 27, Folder 244)
  - International Health Division, Fellowships, 1927-1932 (Box 27, Folder 245-249)
  - International Health Division, Fellowships, 1933-1935 (Box 28, Folder 250-252)
  - International Health Division, Fellowship and Travel Grant Actions, 1936-1938 (Box 28, Folder 235-255)
  - International Health Division, Fellowship and Travel Grant Actions, 1939-1947 (Box 29, Folder 256-261)
  - International Health Division, Fellowship and Travel Grant Actions, 1948-1950 (Box 30, Folder 262-264)
  - International Health Division, Medical Sciences, and Division of Medical and Public Health, New York, Fellowships, 1951-1955 (Box 30, Folder 265-266)
  - International Relations, Grants-in-Aid, 1976-1979 (Box 30, Folder 270)
  - International Relations, Grants-in-Aid, 1980-1985 (Box 31, Folder 271-276)
  - Laura Spelman Rockefeller Memorial, Fellowships, 1929-1930 (Box 31, Folder 277)
  - Medical Education and Public Health, New York, Fellowships, 1955-1959 (Box 31, Folder 278-280)
  - Medical Education and Public Health, New York, Grants-in-Aid, 1955-1956 (Box 31, Folder 281)
  - Medical Education and Public Health, New York, Grants-in-Aid, 1957-1958 (Box 32, Folder 282)
  - Medical Education and Public Health, New York, Grants-in-Aid, Allocations, and Miscellaneous, 1955-1959 (Box 32, Folder 283)
  - Medical Sciences, New York, Fellowships, 1927-1936 (Box 32, Folder 284-288)
  - Medical Sciences, New York, Fellowships, 1937-1950 (Box 33, Folder 289-291)
  - Medical Sciences, Paris, Fellowships, 1929-1935 (Box 33, Folder 292-294)
  - Medical Sciences, Paris, Fellowships, 1936-1940 (Box 34, Folder 295)
  - Medical Sciences, British Medical Students, Grants-in-Aid, 1941-1945 (Box 34, Folder 296)
  - Medical Sciences, New York, Grants-in-Aid, 1932-1951 (Box 34, Folder 297-300)
  - Medical Sciences, Paris, Grants-in-Aid, 1929-1935 (Box 35, Folder 301-305)
  - Medical and Natural Sciences, New York, Fellowships, 1959 (Box 36, Folder 306)
  - Medical and Natural Sciences, Fellowships and Scholarships, 1960-1963 (Box 36, Folder 307-310)
  - Medical and Natural Sciences, Fellowships and Scholarships, 1964-1969 (Box 37, Folder 311-316)
  - Medical and Natural Sciences, Biomedical Sciences, Fellowships & Scholarships, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 317)
  - Medical and Natural Sciences, New York, Grants-in-Aid, 1959 (Box 38, Folder 318)
  - Medical and Natural Sciences, Grants-in-Aid, 1960-1961 (Box 38, Folder 319-322)
  - Medical and Natural Sciences, Grants-in-Aid, 1962-1967 (Box 39, Folder 323-328)
  - Medical and Natural Sciences, Grants-in-Aid, 1968-1969 (Box 40, Folder 329-330)
  - Medical and Natural Sciences, Biomedical Sciences, Grants-in-Aid, 1970 (Box 40, Folder 331)
  - Miscellaneous, 1960-1962 (Box 40, Folder 332-334)
  - Miscellaneous, 1963-1965 (Box 41, Folder 335-340)
  - Miscellaneous, 1966-1968 (Box 42, Folder 341-346)
  - Miscellaneous, Grants-in-Aid, 1969 (Box 43, Folder 347-348)
  - Miscellaneous, 1970-1971 (Box 43, Folder 349-351)
  - Miscellaneous, Vol. I; Vol. II, Donations of Equipment, 1972-1974 (Box 44, Folder 352-357)
  - Miscellaneous, Vol. III, "E" Numbers and Donations of Equipment, 1974 (Box 45, Folder 358)
  - Miscellaneous, Vol. I; Vol. II; Vol. III, "E" Numbers and Donations of Equipment, 1975 (Box 45, Folder 359-361)
  - Miscellaneous, Vol. I; Vol. II, 1976 (Box 45, Folder 362-363)
  - Miscellaneous, Vol. III, "E" Numbers and Donation of Equipment, 1976 (Box 46, Folder 364)
  - Miscellaneous, Vol. I; Vol. II; Vol. III, "E" Numbers and Donation of Equipment, 1977 (Box 46, Folder 365-367)
  - Miscellaneous, Vol. I; Vol. II, 1978 (Box 46, Folder 368-369)
  - Miscellaneous, Vol. III, "E" Numbers and Donation of Equipment, 1978 (Box 47, Folder 370)
  - Miscellaneous, Vol. I; Vol. II, Vol. III, "E" Numbers and Donation of Equipment, 1979 (Box 47, Folder 371-373)
  - Miscellaneous, Vol. I; Vol. II, 1980 (Box 47, Folder 374-375)
  - Miscellaneous, Vol. III, "E" Numbers and Donation of Equipment, 1980 (Box 48, Folder 376)
  - Miscellaneous, Vol. I; Vol. II, Vol. III, "E" Numbers and Donation of Equipment, 1981 (Box 48, Folder 377-379)
  - Miscellaneous, Vol. I, 1982 (Box 48, Folder 380)
  - Miscellaneous, Vol. II, "E" Numbers and Donation Equipment, 1982 (Box 49, Folder 381)
  - Miscellaneous, Vol. I; Vol. II, "E" Numbers and Donation of Equipment, 1983-1984 (Box 49, Folder 382-385)
  - Miscellaneous, Vol. I; Vol. II, "E" Numbers, Donation of Equipment, and Special Postdoctoral Fellowships, 1985 (Box 50, Folder 386-387)
  - Natural Sciences, New York, Fellowships, 1929-1953 (Box 50, Folder 388-391)
  - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, New York, Fellowships, 1954-1955 (Box 51, Folder 392)
  - Natural Sciences, Fellowships, Paris & Peiping, 1929-1933 (Box 51, Folder 393-396)
  - Natural Sciences, Fellowships, Paris, 1934-1935 (Box 51, Folder 397)
  - Natural Sciences, Fellowships, Paris, 1936-1940 (Box 52, Folder 398-399)
  - Natural Sciences, New York, Grants-in-Aid, 1942-1950 (Box 52, Folder 400-402)
  - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, New York, Grants-in-Aid, 1951-1955 (Box 52, Folder 403)
  - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, New York, Grants-in-Aid, 1951-1955 (Box 53, Folder 404-405)
  - Natural Sciences, Paris, Grants-in-Aid, 1929-1940 (Box 53, Folder 406-408)
  - Natural and Environmental Sciences, Fellowships & Scholarships, 1972, 1974 (Box 53, Folder 509)
  - Natural and Environmental Sciences, Fellowships, 1973, 1975-1978 (Box 53, Folder 510-514)
  - Natural and Environmental Sciences, Grants-in-Aid, 1971-1978 (Box 54, Folder 415-422)
  - New York, Miscellaneous, 1929-1949 (Box 54, Folder 423-425)
  - New York, Miscellaneous, 1939-1959 (Box 55, Folder 426-431)
  - New York, Miscellaneous, 1957-1959 (Box 56, Folder 432)
  - Population Division, Fellowships, 1978 (Box 56, Folder 433)
  - Population Sciences, Fellowships, 1979-1985 (Box 56, Folder 434-440)
  - Population Division, Grants-in-Aid, 1978 (Box 56, Folder 441)
  - Population Sciences, Grants-in-Aid, 1979-1983 (Box 56, Folder 442-446)
  - Population Sciences, Grants-in-Aid, 1984-1985 (Box 57, Folder 447-448)
  - Quality of the Environment, Grants-in-Aid, 1979 (Box 57, Folder 449)
  - Refugee Scholar Program, 1940-1944 (Box 57, Folder 450-451)
  - Research Aid, Natural Sciences, 1933-1941 (Box 57, Folder 452-454)
  - Social Sciences, New York, Fellowships, 1929-1959 (Box 58, Folder 455-460)
  - Social Sciences, Paris, Fellowships, 1929-1933 (Box 59, Folder 461-466)
  - Social Sciences, Paris, Fellowships, 1934-1939 (Box 60, Folder 467-471)
  - Social Sciences, Fellowships and Scholarships, 1960-1962 (Box 60, Folder 472-473)
  - Social Sciences, Fellowships and Scholarships, 1971-1974 (Box 61, Folder 474-477)
  - Social Sciences, Fellowships, 1975-1977 (Box 61, Folder 478-480)
  - Social Sciences, Fellowships, 1978 (Box 62, Folder 481)
  - Social Sciences, New York, Grants-in-Aid, 1935-1951 (Box 62, Folder 481-486)
  - Social Sciences, New York, Grants-in-Aid, 1952-1959 (Box 63, Folder 487-490)
  - Social Sciences, New York, Grants-in-Aid and Allocaitons, 1950-1959 (Box 63, Folder 491)
  - Social Sciences, Grants-in-Aid, Paris, 1930-1933 (Box 63, Folder 492)
  - Social Sciences, Paris, Grants-in-Aid, 1934-1940 (Box 64, Folder 493-494)
  - Social Sciences, Grants-in-Aid, 1960-1962, 1971-1974 (Box 64, Folder 495-500)
  - Social Sciences, Grants-in-Aid, 1975-1978 (Box 65, Folder 501-504)
  - Special Interests and Explorations, Grants-in-Aid, 1979-1985 (Box 65, Folder 505-511)
  - Special Postdoctoral Fellowships, 1977-1982 (Box 65, Folder 512)
  - Special Research Aid, Deposed Scholars, New York and Paris, 1933-1940 (Box 66, Folder 513-515)
- Accession 2023:007, 1986-2017; 2; 18.78 Cubic Feet 46 letter document boxes and 1 record storage box
  Arrangement
  Original order, as received.
  - Fellowships and Grants-In-Aid, 1; 5.32 Cubic Feet 14 letter document boxes
    - Fellowships - Population Sciences (PS), 1986-1996 (Box 1, Folder 1-4)
    - Fellowships - Health Sciences (HS), 1986-1993 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Fellowships - Education For Development (EFD), 1986-1988 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Grants-In-Aid - Equal Opportunity (EO), 1986-1999 (Box 2, Folder 2-5)
    - Grants-In-Aid - Agricultural Sciences (AS), 1986-1999 (Box 3, Folder 1-3)
    - Grants-In-Aid - Centers (CE), 1995 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Grants-In-Aid - Building American Democracy (BD), 1996-1998 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Grants-In-Aid - Global Programs (GP), 1999 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Grants-In-Aid - Global Environment (GE), 1990-1999 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Grants-In-Aid - School Reform (SR), 1990-1996 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Grants-In-Aid - Arts and Humanities (AH), 1986-1999 (Box 4, Folder 3-5, Box 5, Folder 1-2)
    - Grants-In-Aid - Special International Initiative (SII), IP, IS, GEE, 1991-1999 (Box 5, Folder 3-4)
    - Grants-In-Aid - Population Sciences (PS), 1986-1999 (Box 5, Folder 5, Box 6, Folder 1-3)
    - Grants-In-Aid - International Relations (IR), 1985 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Grants-In-Aid - Inter-program Special Program (SP), 1987-1991 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Grants-In-Aid - African Initiatives (AI), 1991-1999 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Grants-In-Aid - Health Sciences (HS), 1986-1999 (Box 7, Folder 1-4)
    - Fellowships - Agricultural Sciences (AS), 1986-1999 (Box 7, Folder 5, Box 8, Folder 1-5, Box 9, Folder 1-2)
    - Grants-In-Aid - Special Interests and Explorations (SIE), 1986-1999 (Box 9, Folder 3-5, Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Asian Cities Climate Change Resilience Network, 2014-2017 (Box 43, Folder 3)
      Conditions Governing Access
      Restricted - Open in 2028
    - Girls Education in Africa - Grant Products, c. 1990s (Box 44, Folder 1-2, Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Africa - Grants, 2013-2015 (Box 45, Folder 2, Box 46, Folder 1-2)
      Restricted - Open in 2026
  - Officers' Actions, 2; 11.39 Cubic Feet 30 letter document boxes
    - Officers' Actions - 1986 - Miscellaneous (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Officers' Actions - 1986 - Fellowships and Special Postdoctoral Fellowship (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Officers' Actions - 1987 - Miscellaneous Appropriations/Allocations (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Officers' Actions - 1987 - Special Postdoctoral Fellowship (Social Science Research Fellowship in Population Studies) (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Officers' Actions - 1988 - Miscellaneous Appropriations/Allocations (Box 11, Folder 1-2)
    - Officers' Actions - 1988 - Special Postdoctoral Fellowships (Social Science Research Fellowship in Population Studies) (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Officers' Actions - 1989 - Miscellaneous Appropriations/Allocations (Box 11, Folder 4-5)
    - Officers' Actions - 1990 - Miscellaneous Appropriations/Allocations (Box 12, Folder 1-2)
    - Officers' Actions - 1991 - Miscellaneous Appropriations/Allocations (Box 12, Folder 3, Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Officers' Actions - 1992 - Miscellaneous Appropriations/Allocations (Box 13, Folder 2-3)
    - Officers' Actions - 1993 - Miscellaneous Appropriations/Allocations (Box 14, Folder 1-2)
    - Officers' Actions - 1994 - Miscellaneous Appropriations/Allocations (Box 14, Folder 3, Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Officers' Actions - 1995 - Miscellaneous Appropriations/Allocations (Box 15, Folder 2-3)
    - Officers' Actions - 1996 - Miscellaneous Appropriations/Allocations (Box 16, Folder 1-2)
    - Officers' Actions - 1997 - Miscellaneous Appropriations/Allocations (Box 16, Folder 3, Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Officers' Actions - 1998 - Miscellaneous Appropriations/Allocations (Box 17, Folder 2, Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Officers' Actions - 1999 - Miscellaneous Appropriations/Allocations (Box 18, Folder 2, Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Officers' Grant Actions - 2000 (Box 42, Folder 3, Box 43, Folder 1-2)
    - Officers' Grant Actions - 2001 (Box 19, Folder 2-3, Box 20, Folder 1-3)
    - Officers' Grant Actions - 2002 (Box 20, Folder 4, Box 21, Folder 1-2)
    - Officers' Grant Actions - 2003 (Box 21, Folder 3, Box 22, Folder 1-3)
    - Officers' Grant Actions - 2004 (Box 22, Folder 4, Box 23, Folder 1-3)
    - Officers' Grant Actions - 2005 (Box 23, Folder 4, Box 24, Folder 1-2)
    - Officers' Grant Actions - 2006 (Box 24, Folder 3, Box 25, Folder 1-2)
    - Officers' Grant Actions - 2007 (Box 25, Folder 3, Box 26, Folder 1-2)
    - Officers' Grant Actions - 2008 (Box 26, Folder 2-3)
    - Officers' Grant Actions - 2009 (Box 27, Folder 1-3, Box 28, Folder 1-2)
    - Officers' Grant Actions - 2010 (Box 29, Folder 1-3, Box 30, Folder 1-4, Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Officers' Grant Actions - 2011 (Box 35, Folder 1, Box 36, Box 37, Folder 1-2)
    - Officers' Grant Actions - 2012 (Box 31, Folder 2, Box 32, Folder 1-2, Box 33, Folder 1, Box 38)
  - Consultancy Actions, 3; 2.66 Cubic Feet 7 letter document boxes
    - Consultancy Actions - 1981-1984 (Box 33, Folder 2-5)
    - Consultancy Actions - 1985-1990, 1990-2003 (Box 34, Folder 1-6)
    - Consultancy Actions - 1991-1992 (Box 38, Folder 2-3)
    - Consultancy Actions - 1993-1997 (Box 39, Folder 1-5)
    - Consultancy Actions - 1998-2001 (Box 40, Folder 1-4)
    - Consultancy Actions - 2002-2005 (Box 41, Folder 1-4)
    - Consultancy Actions - 2006-2009 (Box 42, Folder 1-2)
  - Girls Education in Africa - Audiovisual Material, 4; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - Rockefeller Foundation - Orientation Day 1 - Part 1, 2002 January 30; VHS; Sound, 65 minutes (Box 1, Tape AV 13098)
      Access copy currently unavailable. Please contact a RAC archivist for further instruction.
      Scope and Contents
      Introduction by Judith Hamer, Learning Officer (11 minutes); Intro by Robert Giacometti, Director, Human Resources (9 minutes); Gordon Conway, President (43 minutes)
    - Rockefeller Foundation - Orientation Day 1 - Part 2, 2002 January 30; VHS; Sound, 90 minutes (Box 1, Tape AV 13099)
      Robert W. Herdt, Vice President (50 minutes); Donna J. Dean, Treasurer and Chief Investment Officer (40 minutes)
    - Rockefeller Foundation - Orientation Day 2 - Part 1, 2002 February 13; VHS; Sound, 80 minutes (Box 1, Tape AV 13100)
      Robert Giacometti, Director, Human Resources (9 minutes); James Allen Smith. Historian (51 minutes); Robert L. Bach, Global Inclusion (18 minutes)
    - Rockefeller Foundation - Orientation Day 2 - Part 2, 2002 February 13; VHS; Sound, 83 minutes (Box 1, Tape AV 13101)
      Gary Toenniessen, Food Security (17 minutes); Darren C. Walker, Working Communities (14 minutes); Timothy G. Evans, Health Equity (29 minutes); Raymund A. Paredes, Creativity and Culture (11 minutes); Question and Answer - Gary Toenniessen (12 minutes)
    - Rockefeller Foundation - Orientation Day 3 - Part 1, 2002 March 6; VHS; Sound, 95 minutes (Box 1, Tape AV 13102)
      Lynda Mullen, Secretary of the Corporation (62 minutes); Andre C. Oliver, Associate Director, Communications (16 minutes); Fernando Mola-Davis, Manager, Information Technology (17 minutes)
    - Rockefeller Foundation - Orientation Day 3 - Part 2, 2002 March 6; VHS; Sound, 80 minutes (Box 1, Tape AV 13103)
      Robert Giacometti, Director, Human Resources (49 minutes); ICORE (23 minutes); Sal LaSpada, Staff Council (7 minutes)
    - Southeast Asia Regional Program and Africa Regional Program, 2002 March 13; VHS; Sound, 34 minutes (Box 1, Tape AV 13104)
      Rosalia Sciortino, Southeast Asia Regional Program (16 minutes); Cheikh Mbacké, Africa Regional Program (18 minutes)
    - "Send Your Girl Child to School", c. 1994; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 1, Tape AV 15860)
      1. Full Length English Version 2. English/French Version 3. Abbreviated English/French Version
    - "Send Your Girl Child to School", c. 1994; VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 13093)
    - "These Girls are Missing", c. 1995; VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 13094)
      Camerini-Robertson Documentary Films
    - "The Girls Know It", circa 1995; VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 13095)
    - "A Woman's Alternative", VHS; Sound, color (Box 1, Tape AV 13096)
      Video Sewa Productions
    - "Our Body, Our Life", VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 13097)